(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-08-30T00:24:34.659923",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
Hey!
Bau bau!
Welcome to our 3rd Anniversary Live
celebration of hololive!
And thanks to hololive,
we are so glad we started hololive!
Here we go!
RED HEART!
One, two, three, go!
Hi, how are you?
Are you calling up my phone?
Baby tell me what is wrong,
don't you ever let me go
Hi, I am good,
I am still looking for proof
Am I good enough for you?
Don't you tell me what's my rule
This is me,
are you coming on the ride?
We are going super high,
got to be who what I like
You and me,
are you ready for the fight?
Alright, alright, alright
Stronger than I've ever been before
This is who I am,
nothing in the way
...far away, you and me make the part of me.
I give you my big red heart
my, my big red heart, my, my big red heart
I'll be true to my big red heart
my red heart
Hi! Over there, thank you for coming along
on this journey of my own, promise me you won't let go
Yes, this is me, I am falling but I'm strong
'cause you've got me in your arms, don't you ever let me go
I want you to come with me on the ride
this is going super high, I am falling from the sky
Got to be who you wanna be, that's right, alright, alright, alright
Let's go!
One, two, three, four!
Hi! Hi! Hi! Hi! Hi! Hi! Hi! Hi! Haachama! Haachama!
Hi! Hi! Hi! Hi! Hi! Hi! Hi! Hi!
I am still a girl, figuring out what's true or false in this whole wide world
I'm your only girl, tell me once more what's really going on with you
I'm looking for the right one on the road, the one that'll always take me back to you
This can be home, will you be my home?
Stronger than I've ever been before, this is who I am
nothing in the way, today and far away, you and me, we make the part of me
I give you my big red heart, my, my big red heart, my, my big red heart
I'll be true to my big red heart, my, my big red heart, my, my big red heart
my, my red heart
ばうばう～！
Bau bau~!
Thank you so much, Ruffians, for coming to FuwaMoco's 3rd Anniversary Live,
Thanks to Hololive! ばうばう！
Thanks to Hololive! Bau bau!
フワモコの3周年記念ライブ「Thanks to Hololive」にきてくれて本当にありがとう！
Thank you so much for coming to FuwaMoco's 3rd Anniversary Live, "Thanks to Hololive"!
ありがとう！ばうばう！
Thank you! Bau bau!
Yeah! Today, our entire concert is to share our love and appreciation
for Hololive, our senpai, teammates, kohai, and you, Ruffians!
そう！今日、3周年を記念して、今日はホロライブへの思いと
Yes! To celebrate our 3rd anniversary,
感謝の気持ちを伝えるために、思いっきり歌って踊ります！
we'll sing and dance with all our might to convey our love and gratitude!
And this stage is going to be packed with all of our love for Hololive! Get ready, okay?
イェーイ！うん！
Yeah! Yeah!
And, of course, you do want to know our hashtag, right?
Yeah, very important! Our hashtag for today is...
#FWMC3rd!
Please take lots of screenshots, pasha-pasha, and tweet about us on SNS, okay? ばうばう！
Please take lots of screenshots, pasha-pasha, and tweet about us on SNS, okay? Bau bau!
うん！そう、ハッシュタグは「#FWMC3rd」で、スクリーンショットを
Yep! That's right, use the hashtag "#FWMC3rd" and post
たくさんSNSに投稿してね！待ってるよ！
lots of screenshots on SNS! We'll be waiting!
もうちょっと行くからね！
We'll go check them right away!
おー、ぽちぽち！おー何するの、ぽちぽち！何言ってんの？オッケー！
Ooh, click-click! What are you doing? Click-click! What are you saying? Okay!
Yeah, we're waiting! ばうばう！
Yeah, we're waiting! Bau bau!
But, our very first song that we performed was Haachama-senpai's RED HEART!
It's a very precious song of ours. And, you know, it's because of Haachama-senpai that actually, FuwaMoco...
We found Hololive!
フワモコはね、はあちゃま先輩のおかげでホロライブに出会えましたから、とってもとっても大切な曲です
Because it's thanks to Haachama-senpai that FuwaMoco discovered Hololive, so it's a very, very precious song to us.
We love you so much, Haachama-senpai! We're waiting to collab again, okay?
そう、はあちゃま先輩大好きー！
Yes, we love you so much, Haachama-senpai!
やったよ！やったよ！ポンポン！
We did it! We did it! Pump it up!
見て、これ！
Look at this!
ステージ！
Stage!
イェーイ！
Yeah!
We designed today's stage with a very special hololive-themed design!
そう！
That's right!
そう、今回のステージはホロライブをテーマに作ってもらいました！
Yes, this stage was made with a hololive theme!
イェーイ！ポンポン！
Yeah! Pump it up!
We really hope that our love for hololive will reach you today.
Yeah, we'll be singing and dancing, of course, with some very special senpais, so please look forward to it!
うん！
Yeah!
お？
Oh?
Well, there might be a big announcement, too!
そして、そして、重大発表もあるから...
And, and, we also have a major announcement...
離れず、最後まで見てください！
...so don't go away, please watch until the very end!
Oh, please watch to the very end, okay?
Stay tuned!
イェーイ！
Yeah!
ハッピー三周年！
Happy third anniversary!
来てくれた！
You made it!
We're here for the world!
ハッピー三周年！ハッピー三周年！
Happy third anniversary! Happy third anniversary!
アドベントのみんながお祝いに来てくれました！
The rest of Advent came here to celebrate with us!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
Yeah, but you know, we just celebrated our third anniversary of Advent a few weeks ago!
Yeah, it was such a fun time, but now...
...we're in our fourth year!
え！？四年目！？
Wait, fourth year?!
四年目！？
Fourth year?!
四年目！？おめでとう！
Fourth year?! Congratulations!
四年目早いね！
Fourth year is so fast!
But before it's time to have an interview...
しおりん！
Shiorin!
Do you have anything to say?
Happy third anniversary!
It's been really nuts if you think about it...
...because we've had the evolution of getting to know each other from the very first collab game...
...to now, three years later, we give each other little silly gifts...
...gnomes, a little cute plushie bookmark...
...and I just really appreciate being everyone's friend.
Let's be friends for many more years to come, yes?
イェーイ！ありがとう！
Yeah! Thank you!
ネルたん！
Nerissa!
ネルたん？
Nerissa?
Well, of course, it's Fuwamoco Day, so...
...obviously talking about you, but keep in mind, I do feel this way about all of Advent.
It's applicable to everyone.
個人宛じゃないんだね。
It's not personal.
You know, since we all got together, it's just been so clear...
...that all of us were meant to be friends, if you know what I mean.
そうだね。
Yeah.
Like, I truly can't imagine being in a gen with more hard-working and amazing people than you guys...
...and every day, I'm just so, so grateful to be able to have you guys here...
...as my friends and as my genmates. I'm so happy.
ありがとう！大好き！
Thank you! We love you!
三周年おめでとうございます！
Happy third anniversary!
ポンポン！イェーイ！
Pump it up! Yeah!
Hug her again!
イェーイ！ハグ！
Yeah! Hug!
大好き！ありがとう！
We love you! Thank you!
All right, let me hold your paws while I say this.
All right, Fuwamoco...
...三周年、三周年おめでとうございます！
...happy third, third anniversary!
イェーイ！ポンポン！
Yeah! Pump it up!
You know, we've been through so much together as Advent, and...
...without you guys, you know, like, you fed me bugs...
うんうん。
Yeah.
...you got me muscle wave...
...you made sure I didn't die...
...you held my hand...
...you held my hand as I crossed the street...
...and I couldn't imagine like starting this journey with anybody else other than you guys.
So, I'm so happy we're here celebrating today.
Me too, Biboo! We're the worst of Advent together!
イェーイ！
Yeah!
It's really been an amazing three years.
うんうん。
Yeah.
You know what?
We love you!
イェーイ！大好き！
Yeah! We love you!
Let's continue strong together!
But you know, our concert is only just starting, right?
そう！
That's right!
We should sing together, the five of us, you know?
Well, Mococo, we wanted to sing a song that means so much to us.
Right, you know. Without our senpais' hard work, we all wouldn't be here, you know?
And when we all debuted...
...there was five senpais who were just about to celebrate their third anniversary, too.
そう、だから...
Yeah, so...
...with all the love and respect in our hearts, please listen to this very special version of...
...hololive English -Myth-'s original song.
Here we go...
Reunion!
Sing out boldly again,
continuing this odyssey.
We'll start this new refrain brimming with memories!
And when the clouded skies become bright, let's reunite!
This is a precious song filled with memories sung with the very senpais who started Hololive English!
We'll put all our love and respect into it as Advent!
Ready? Set? Stream!
It's almost showtime, are you ready?
It's not tomorrow, it's today!
But when times are ruff,
is it really enough?
Cause they're chasing me endlessly, why?
Take it easy, what have we learned?
When the Cell doors open, it's our turn!
We can do this, call the Adventrix!
Teach new dogs all of our tricks!
Been on the run for so long that we really hit our stride!
Now look at all we've accomplished together side by side!
Dreamers to streamers to entertainers to senpai!!
Justice ketch-getcha!
Mogojan, behind you!
Spanning new dimensions,
we can bring another mystery to light!
Planning our ascension,
dancing in flight, we ignite...
Through the stories we inspire,
we can light another fire,
Advent's reaching even higher!
Through this world and beyond,
our distant dreams have brought us here.
A strong, unyielding bond,
guiding us endlessly,
will bring us moments that we hold dear.
Time rushes on,
and though these winds may scatter us,
We'll keep this promise:
When the moment's finally right,
we'll always find a way to reunite!
I'll lend a helping paw, I can go the extra mile,
I'm gonna give my all, so let's protect your smile!
I'm rocking in again, now I'll never break my streak!
Gaming streams full of memes six or seven times a week, yeah!
It's time for a pup talk, cause I know it's essential,
but even when we're in the doghouse, we got endless potential!
It's time for paws-itive thoughts,
so I keep on pondering donuts!
But now I'm getting warm and fuzzy
from the love that you've shown us, bau bau!
Countless moments
led us to this day: triumph and sorrow,
hope for tomorrow...
we'll always find our way,
come what may!
In every universe,
we were always meant to meet.
I'll lead a boundless search,
We will never know defeat.
My wings will guide your hands
as the fateful days go by,
We will cut a path
through a never-ending sky!
Shining bright together,
I can sense another wish is coming true.
We'll be friends fur-ever,
loyal and true,
me and you!
Sing out again!
The clouded skies give way to clear;
We'll start this new refrain brimming with memories!
Another story's starting right here...
We'll keep forging ahead to make a saga all our own!
Whichever paths we tread,
steadily journeying,
we know we're never really alone...
If we believe
wherever fate may find us,
our love will bind us,
Every epic chapter we write
will set us on the path to reunite!
We love you all from the bottom of our hearts!
Let's continue LIGHTING THE FIRE and spreading Hololive across the world!
Step and Go!!
絵の奥から止まったような時計
Like a clock stopped deep inside the frame,
幼い頃の歌 思い出して
remembering a song from my childhood.
もう心配しなくてもいいよ
You don't need to worry anymore...
あの優しい声が
because that gentle voice...
そばにあったから
was right by my side.
恋に傷ついて
There were days when I was hurt by love...
道に迷った日もあったけれど
and lost my way, but...
いつだって探してたのは
what I was always searching for...
輝けるはずの better day
was a better day that should shine.
everyday 解き放て
Every day, let loose...
ためらいがちなその emotion
that hesitant emotion!
時代のせいにしたってつまらないよ
Blaming the times is so boring.
everyday 君であれ
Every day, be yourself,
立ち止まる日もあるけれど
even though there are days when you stop.
ねえきっと君は大丈夫
Hey, I'm sure you'll be fine!
step and go!!
誰もが記憶の中にある
Everyone has deep within their memories...
大事なあの笑顔抱きしめてる
embracing that precious smile.
いつか君にまた会えたなら
If I can meet you again someday...
素直にちゃんと
I want to honestly...
気持ち伝えたい
convey my feelings properly.
自分自身で引いたボーダーライン
If it's a boundary line you drew yourself...
ならさあ飛び越えて
come on, jump over it!
いつでも描いていこうよ
Always, let's draw...
君らしい色で better day
a better day in your own colors.
everyday きらめいて
Every day, sparkle...
今動き出したemotion
with the emotion that started moving now!
誰かのせいにしたってつまらないよ
Blaming someone else is so boring.
everyday らしくあれ
Every day, be yourself,
やがてこの雨も上がって
eventually this rain will clear up too.
ねえきっと君は大丈夫
Hey, I'm sure you'll be fine!
step and go!!
挑んだ数だけ
As many times as you take on the challenge...
涙は出るけど
tears will fall, but...
止まない雨はないように
just like there's no rain that doesn't stop...
君ならできるよ step and go!!
you can do it, step and go!!
everyday 解き放て
Every day, let loose...
ためらいがちなその emotion
that hesitant emotion!
時代のせいにしたってつまらないよ
Blaming the times is so boring.
everyday 君であれ
Every day, be yourself,
立ち止まる日もあるけれど
even though there are days when you stop.
ねえきっと君は大丈夫
Hey, I'm sure you'll be fine!
step and go!!
FuwaMocoの居場所である大好きなhololiveを作ってくれてありがとう
Thank you for creating Hololive, our beloved home.
でいり〜たいり〜!
Daily Diary!
とどけちゃおう
Let's deliver it!
青春実施中
Youth is in progress,
挑戦配信中
our challenge is broadcasting!
青春実施中
Youth is in progress,
挑戦配信中
our challenge is broadcasting!
今日もね
Today, too,
楽しいは発見
fun is discovered!
また新しい 好きが見つかったよ
I found a new love again!
お、何? テンション上がる!
Oh, what? Getting hyped!
近所にできたカフェの
At the cafe that opened nearby,
ケーキ
the cake...
なんかすごく美味しかったんだよ
was somehow really delicious!
食レポになってないでしょ!
That's not a food review!
知らなかったゲームや
Games I didn't know about,
聴いたことない歌
songs I've never heard before...
ちょっと気になったら手伸ばしちゃう
if I'm a bit curious, I'll reach out for them!
ほら ほら
Look, look,
一緒に遊ぼう
let's play together!
10連ガチャ引いちゃおう!
Let's do a 10-pull gacha!
歌ってみよう
Let's sing!
ホラ、ゲームやってみよう
Look, let's play a game!
あの曲、歌ってみよう
Let's try singing that song!
全部がもう楽しいの
Everything is already so much fun!
窓の向こうの
Beyond the window,
笑顔に手を振っちゃおう
let's wave to the smiling faces!
アニメ 視聴中
I'm watching anime!
発見！
Discovered!
モブのキャラに乗せるポテンシャル
Finding potential in background characters!
ヤバ！見る目あるわ！
No way! You have a good eye!
深夜の定番番組や 名作
Late-night staple shows and masterpieces...
思いついた新ネタ 爆笑
The new jokes we came up with... hilarious!
当たらない天気予報もきっと
Even the inaccurate weather forecast
面白いことになるんだよ
will surely turn into something fun!
聞いて聞いて今朝の朝
Listen, listen! This morning...
目覚ましならなくって
my alarm didn't go off,
寝過ごしちゃったのは
and the reason I overslept was...
昨晩の生放送
...last night's livestream!
すごく楽しんで
I had so much fun,
寝付けなかったんだ
I couldn't fall asleep!
特別すごいことなんてそう起こらないリアル
In reality, amazing things rarely happen.
だけどそのエッセンス
But that essence...
仮想な世界
turns a virtual world...
夢に変えて 毎日がパラダイス
...into a dream, making every day a paradise!
思い切り遊んで 笑っちゃおう
Let's play with all our might and laugh together!
対戦実況！イェーイ！
Match commentary! Yay!
全部無くす覚悟してきた
I came prepared to lose everything!
なにそれ！
What's that?!
負ける気はしないんだって！
I don't plan on losing!
諦めたら実況終了だよ！
If you give up, the stream is over!
えー！まだ終わりたくない！
Eh! I don't want it to end yet!
どんな毎日も 楽しくなっちゃうんだ
Any kind of day will become fun!
だっていつだって ほら
Because always, look...
あなたが待ってるの
...you are waiting for us!
みんなで毎日を
Sharing every day with everyone,
出会えた嬉しいを
happy that we met,
みんなと一緒に
together with everyone,
気分はもう最高潮
our spirits are at their peak!
窓の向こうの
Beyond the window,
笑顔に手を振って
wave to the smiling faces,
配信で届ける でいりぃだいありぃ
and deliver our Daily Diary through our stream!
青春実況中
Youth commentary in progress,
挑戦配信中
challenge streaming in progress!
青春実況中
Youth commentary in progress,
挑戦配信中
challenge streaming in progress!
でいりぃだいありぃ 届けよう
Let's deliver our Daily Diary!
[画面: みんな大～すきだよー！！]
[Screen: We love you all so much!!]
[画面: 3年分のDaily Diaryをみんなと一緒に
紡ぎ出せたのは最高の宝物]
[Screen: Being able to weave three years of Daily Diary
together with you is our greatest treasure.]
Ruffians! And that was Daily Diary!
We were really happy to perform it together with
Miko-senpai, Korone-senpai, and Watame-senpai! Bau bau!
But the reason why we chose Daily Diary... is because...
Daily Diary is a really special song to us.
We listened to it lots and lots before our debut,
and we really, really, just really wanted to start
creating our own Daily Diary together with you all!
And also, listening to it over and over,
we kept on imagining...
...what that might look like!
そう、ふわもこにとって でいりぃだいありぃはすごく大切な曲で
Yes, Daily Diary is an extremely important song for Fuwamoko,
デビュー前にたくさん聴いてた曲です
and we listened to it a lot before our debut.
あの頃の気持ちは今でもすごく覚えてて
Even now, we still clearly remember how we felt back then.
早くデビューしてみんなとの でいりぃだいありぃが
作りたくて作りたくて、しょうがなかったんですね
We wanted to debut as soon as possible and start
making our Daily Diary with everyone so badly!
でも、この3年間でみんなと作ってきた思い出が
But the memories we've made with everyone
over these past three years...
想像以上に素晴らしい でいりぃだいありぃになってるよ！
...have turned into a Daily Diary
more wonderful than we ever imagined!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
And all the memories we've made together have formed
an even more wonderful Daily Diary than we could have ever imagined.
Thank you all for everything!
But! You know, I think we still have a lot more coming up,
including... including Fuwamoko's...
...super duper big announcement!
重大告知まであと少しだよ！
There's only a little bit left until the major announcement!
So make sure you stay with us until the very end!
But we still have some very special songs we'd like to sing for you.
"I'm a little nervous, Mococo-chan."
"I'm nervous too!"
"Well, let's get ready, Mococo-chan."
"Okay!"
"Let's get going, okay?"
"Bye-bye!"
君のヒロインは誰？
Who is your heroine?
覚えてる優しさ
I remember your kindness.
君の言葉にきゅんとして
My heart skipped a beat at your words.
上手に言えない
I can't say it well,
代わりに笑いかけてみたの
so I tried smiling at you instead.
目が合った気がしたそれだけで
Just feeling like our eyes met,
鼓動跳ねた
made my heart leap.
お願い 勘違いじゃありませんように
Please, let it not just be my imagination.
そっと心の中で熱い視線送った
I silently sent a passionate gaze from my heart,
振り向いてと願っちゃってた
hoping you would turn around.
ヒロインオーディション エントリーしたならば私
If I were to enter the heroine audition,
ねぇ選んでくれるかな
would you choose me?
真面目のせい？書く
Blame my seriousness? Just writing...
「おはよ」だけで伝わるよ
even a simple "Good morning" gets it across.
何気ないつぶやき
At your casual post,
もしかしてと期待してる
I wonder and secretly hope.
眩しい素敵な人ばかりで
Since you're surrounded by dazzling, wonderful people,
自信もなくて
I lack confidence.
それでも本音では
But deep down in my heart...
365日もっと近づきたい
I want to get closer to you 365 days a year.
私なりのペースになるけど
Even if it's at my own pace.
ヒロインオーディション 勇気を出したら君は
If I gather my courage for the heroine audition,
ねぇ答えてくれるかな
will you answer me?
出会った一瞬からすごいミラクル
It's been an amazing miracle since the instant we met.
このチャンスは赤い糸
This chance is our red thread of fate.
ぎゅっと手繰り寄せて運命にしよう
Let's pull it close and make it destiny.
信じてまっすぐ背伸びの言葉にして
Believing in it, I'll stretch myself to speak directly to you.
君のヒロインは誰？
Who is your heroine?
きっと君の心を動かしてみせるよ
I'll surely show you I can move your heart.
まだまだ全部足りないけど
Though I'm still lacking in so many ways.
ヒロインオーディション 選んでそして私を
For the heroine audition, choose me, and then...
いつかギュッとしてほしい
I want you to hold me tight someday.
ありがとうずっと大好きだよ
Thank you, I'll love you forever!
もういいじゃん むきになっちゃって
Forget it, you're getting so worked up,
カッコつけて カッコよくない
trying to look cool when you're not.
そういうの嫌になってんだ
I'm sick of that stuff,
ほっといてよ 知りたくない
leave me alone, I don't want to know.
もういいじゃん やけになってるの
Forget it, are you acting out?
嫉妬したり じっとできない
Being jealous, unable to sit still.
聞こえないよ 耳塞いだって
I can't hear you, even if I plug my ears,
入ってくるじゃん しんどいな
it still gets in, how annoying.
僕は誰も覗かないよ
I won't peek at anyone else.
だから僕のことそっとしておいて
So just leave me be,
うざい
you're annoying.
たいただけでバカに はい はい はい 受ける
To those fools who just chirped, "Sure, sure, sure, so funny!"
また残して待ってるね とか
"I saved some and I'm waiting for you," or whatever.
本当は怯えている Nus
In truth you're terrified,
吠えるだけの弱虫だったった
just a barking coward.
痛くって泣いたって はい はい はい いつも
Even if it hurts and I cry, "Sure, sure, sure," I'm always...
独りよがりばっかの僕は
just being self-satisfied.
壁を張ったまま笑う
Smiling behind my walls,
それ以上近づかないでってって
saying "Don't get any closer to me."
壊れちゃう
I'll break.
ばかばっか
Nothing but idiots.
ばかばっか やだ ばかばっか
Nothing but idiots, no way, nothing but idiots!
もういいじゃん まだ怒ってるの
Forget it, are you still mad?
ほっといてよ ほっとけないy
Leave me alone! I can't leave you alone.
見ないように 目を逸らしたって
Even if I look away to avoid seeing,
ついてくるじゃん やっぱり
you still follow me after all.
転がったら起きればいいじゃん
If you fall, just get back up!
失ってるから飛べばいいじゃん
If you've lost, just fly!
いやいやいやいや それでよくない？
No, no, no, no, isn't that fine?
間違ったら直せばいいじゃん
If you make a mistake, just fix it!
嫌だったらやめればいいじゃん
If you don't like it, just quit!
いやいやいやいや それでよくない？
No, no, no, no, isn't that fine?
僕は誰も覗かないよ
I won't peek at anyone else.
…ないよ
...anyway.
だから僕のことそっとしておいて
So please just leave me alone.
嫌なこと全部大丈夫と言えたらいいのにな
I wish I could say I'm fine with all the bad things.
思い通りにいったらいいのにな
I wish everything would go my way.
侵害 歌ったら相容れない大正解 いつも僕はそんなロールなの
Infringement, if I sing it, it's an incompatible success, I'm always in that kind of role.
待って 言いたいこと殺したからもう忘れてくれ
Wait, I killed what I wanted to say, so just forget it.
うわははは
Uwahahaha
塞いだだけの馬鹿にハイハイハイ ウケる またのお越し待ってるね
To the idiot who just shut themselves in, "Yeah, yeah, yeah", hilarious! We look forward to your next visit.
だとか 本当は怯えてる 吠えるだけの弱虫だったった
Or something like that, but honestly I'm terrified, I was just a cowardly dog barking.
痛いくせに 吐いて ハイハイハイ
Even though it hurts, you throw up, "Yeah, yeah, yeah".
いつも平気なフリばっかりの僕は
I'm always just pretending to be fine.
壁を貼ったまま笑う それ以上近づかないで とか
Laughing while keeping my walls up, "Don't get any closer than that" or something...
嘘ばっかばっか いい加減馬鹿
Nothing but lies, you utter fool.
とんだバグばっか 出せなせって
Nothing but crazy bugs, "show it" you say.
そんな言葉っかも僕もやっぱ どうしようもないバカでジョーカー
With nothing but those words, I guess I'm just a helpless fool and a joker.
痛いのと堪えられないないない 死ねるって僕の口ばっかだね
Hurting and unbearable, no no no, saying "I can die" is all just talk from my mouth.
今日も壁を貼ったまま笑う それ以上近づかないでってって<
Today, too, I laugh with my walls up, saying "Don't get any closer".
怖いじゃん
It's scary, isn't it?
馬鹿 馬鹿 ほら 馬鹿 馬鹿
Fool, fool, look, fool, fool.
TeddyLoid
ちゅ、ちゅ、ちゅ、ちゅ、ちゅ、ちゅ、ちゅー
Chu, chu, chu, chu, chu, chu, chuu
何気ない声が そわそわ
Your casual voice makes me fidgety.
ちょっと妄想が...居ないな まだまだだって
My little delusions... "They're not here, not yet," I say.
いつからかそれが眩しくなる
Since when did that start becoming so dazzling?
Ah ah
気付いてんじゃない？きっと曖昧そんな言葉で
Haven't you noticed? Surely with such vague words...
Ah ah
もう始まってて ねぇ射ち抜いて 射ち抜いて
It's already started, hey, shoot me through, shoot me through.
だから今落ちてくのって何故だか
So why am I falling right now?
脈打つ鼓動倍して<
My pulsing heartbeat doubles...
渦巻く恋熱く愛して<
...hotly loving this swirling passion.
もう君は最低だ 叶わないな
You're already the worst. I can't compete.
君のきゅーぴっどです また夢中 夢中
I'm your Cupid, crazy in love again.
きっと夢にでてくる
You'll surely appear in my dreams.
ちゅ ちゅ ちゅ ちゅ ちゅ ちゅ ちゅ
Chu, chu, chu, chu, chu, chu, chu
痛いのよ今も
It still hurts even now.
きゅーぴっどです また夢中 夢中
I'm Cupid, crazy in love again.
ちょっと何だって出来る
I can do absolutely anything.
ちゅ ちゅ ちゅ ちゅ ちゅ ちゅ ちゅ
Chu, chu, chu, chu, chu, chu, chu
ぎゅっと抱きしめて
Hold me tight.
どうして
Why?
らったった らしったった らしったった
Rat-tat-ta, rat-tat-ta, rat-tat-ta
君はまだ知らない事情 私も見えてないでしょう
The circumstances you still don't know, I probably can't see them either.
なっちゃった なっちゃった なっちゃった なっちゃった
I became, I became, I became, I became...
あの子には見せてあげる秘事
The secrets I will show to that girl...
思うだけで熱上昇
Just thinking about it makes my temperature rise.
愛だ、さあ、その眼差し
It's love, come on, that look in your eyes.
探し続けた宝石みたい
Like the jewel I kept searching for.
でも、まだまだ、キスすることは禁止だ
But it's still far too early, kissing is forbidden!
うかつする私も愛して<
Love me even when I make careless mistakes.
恋づく魅力も愛して<
Love my love-struck charm as well.
もう私最低だ やめられないから
I'm already the worst. I can't stop.
君のきゅーぴっどです また夢中 夢中
I'm your Cupid, crazy in love again.
もっと欲しくなってくる
I'm starting to want you even more.
ちゅ ちゅ ちゅ ちゅ ちゅ ちゅ ちゅ
Chu, chu, chu, chu, chu, chu, chu
期待をしちゃうよ
I'll start getting my hopes up.
ギブ＆ラブ 感情移入 ずっと気持ち溢れる
Give & Love, empathy, my feelings are always overflowing.
ちゅ ちゅ ちゅ ちゅ ちゅ ちゅ ちゅ
Chu, chu, chu, chu, chu, chu, chu
ぎゅっと抱きしめて
Hold me tight.
あぁ、もう隠せないけど 止まらない鼓動
Ah, I can't hide it anymore, this unstoppable throbbing.
夢から覚めて 気づいて今
Wake up from the dream and realize it now.
We'd run right through
those nights
...inside this labyrinth of lights
there was madness in the meaning
never laughless, we were screaming at the top
of our lungs to the numbness, this city never died
I'll fly, no proof
those heights, I'll never find another chance to say "hey, thanks for saving my life"
I was hopeless, it was stinging
running roadless, we were singing
at the top of our lungs to the numbness, this city never died
what was the root of it all? I couldn't say
used to jump and then fall, rugged and clichéd
would shrug it off without complaint, not a sound
no use in trying to find friends, 'cause in the end nobody sticks around
it's when you shoved yourself into a crowded place
that you turned around and found yourself in love in outer space
cue the reckless nights, no strings, laughing at our own dreams, just what the hell was so funny?
bark up the wrong tree, stumble, used to falling great heights
amidst a concrete jungle, singing 'cause it felt right
we mixed the ennui and troubles, rhyming our discontent
and though it's history, I can't forget the time that we spent
convinced that this could mean another end
exists between real and pretend
a twisted alter-fiction where I missed my chance, did not ascend, and
disappearing into the mist of "never happened" is the me that I can never befriend
I let it go, fade in, fade out
this crazy dream
without a direction, floating aimlessly
there's nothing left back there for me
breathe in, but it won't stop the rain from pouring
we'd run right through those nights
I'll never find my way back to you inside this labyrinth of lights
there was madness in the meaning
never laughless, we were screaming at the top
of our lungs to the numbness, this city never died
but was there ever a soul inside?
chasing fireflies between the soaring high-rises
left a trail behind, defined it "wasted time of our lives"
silent singer, overworked and underpaid
thinks an office is a coffin until off is where you're laid
yet a thought persists, an optimist who ought to be afraid
saw the "nothing wrong" in writing songs behind the lonely shade
is the world a sadder place without the words that you conveyed?
when the ladder fell and shattered every bar that we had played?
does it matter in the end the sound diminished and decayed
and your friends grew tired of fantasy; you're wishing they had stayed?
you don't get to say "I miss you," you watched your heroes fade
into the rear-view mirror of the villain you portrayed
stop the pity party, listen, you don't get to be dismayed
you don't get to be emotional, feel blessed you got it made
these the best of years of life because you chose to make a trade
recollect the days you hoped and you prayed for this
what is there to miss?
fade in, fade out
this hazy dream
without a direction, roaming aimlessly
there's nothing left back there for me
pretend it's the end of a made-up story
I'll fly, no proof
those heights, I'll never find another chance to say "hey, thanks for saving my life"
I was hopeless, it was stinging
driving roadless, we were singing
at the top of our lungs to the numbness, this city never died
I'll say goodbye to the soul inside
and yet somehow, there was romance
in our self-hate, "we've got no chance"
in this light maze, but let's hold hands
through the night haze, we'll run so fast
'til the school chime, 'til the train runs
we know it's time, we're the sane ones
waking up now, to the "real life"
let me daydream, 'til the next night
I'll keep waiting
I'll keep waiting for you
It was the trade of a lifetime, but we won't forget the past!!
We're so thankful! Thank you for being a senpai + friend who has shown us the way and continues to inspire us!!
waking up now, to my real life
let me daydream, 'til the next flight
drowning so long, I got older
now the crowd's gone, is it over?
is it over?
NEW SONG! 一途ってトレンド♡
[New Song: Devoted is trendy♡]
さて♡お教えしましょう♡粋な恋のルールを♡
Now, let me teach you... the stylish rules of love!
いい？♡女の子は♡私だけなの♡
Got it? I'm the only girl for you!
もし、申し訳ございません♡あなたの世界には
If— oh, I am so sorry! In your world...
他の一人居場所なんてあるはずないの
...there shouldn't be room for anyone else!
誰もが羨むレベルで愛してよ
Love me to a level that makes everyone jealous!
思わず真似してみたくなるような恋しよう
Let's fall in love in a way that makes others want to copy us!
ねぇ♡流行っちゃってる Lovy-Dovy 一途ってトレンド♡
Hey, look, lovey-dovey is in style! Devotion is the trend! ♡
よそ見なんてね Darling Darling 時代遅れなの
Looking away, Darling Darling, is so outdated!
Only One どうしよう Suki Suki いつだって私でしょ
You're my only one, what should I do? Suki Suki, it's always me, right?
あなたはほら♡最先端でいてよ
Come on, you need to stay on the cutting edge!
じゃあ♡教えてよ♡あなたの頭の中
Then tell me... what's inside your head?
照れくさそうな目も♡私のものよ♡
Even your shy gaze belongs to me!
少しの秘密も二人あり得ないわ
Even the slightest secret is unacceptable between us!
全てを預けて隠し事なんて無しだよ
Entrust everything to me, absolutely no hiding things!
ねぇ♡気付いちゃってる Lovy-Dovy 従っておトレンド♡
Hey, have you noticed? Lovey-dovey, obeying is the trend! ♡
秘密なんてね Darling Darling 蚊帳の外なのよ
Secrets, Darling Darling, are totally left out in the cold!
正直どうしよう Suki Suki 永遠に結びましょう
Honestly, what should we do? Suki Suki, let's tie the knot forever!
あなたはほら♡最先端でいてよ
Come on, you need to stay on the cutting edge!
どんな時も♡胸を震わせてね
Always make my heart flutter, okay?
離れてても♡ほらあなたってそうあなたって
Even when we're apart, see? You, yes, you...
こんなに素敵なの♡
...are just so wonderful!
この世のこの世の終わりまで　何から何まで繋ぎましょう
Until the end of this world, let's connect everything from A to Z!
私の私の宝物　そうでしょ？そうでしょ？恋しよう
My, my precious treasure. Right? Right? Let's fall in love!
ねぇ♡流行っちゃってる Lovy-Dovy 一途ってトレンド♡
Hey, look, lovey-dovey is in style! Devotion is the trend! ♡
よそ見なんてね Darling Darling 時代遅れなの
Looking away, Darling Darling, is so outdated!
Only One どうしよう Suki Suki いつだって私でしょ
You're my only one, what should I do? Suki Suki, it's always me, right?
あなたはほら♡最先端でいてよ
Come on, you need to stay on the cutting edge!
私だけでいてよ♡
Keep your eyes only on me!
お願い（お願い）私だけよ♡
Please (please), only me!
（お願い　お願い）私だけでいてよ♡
(Please, please) keep your eyes only on me!
お願い（お願い）私だけよ♡
Please (please), only me!
（お願い　お願い）私だけでいてよ♡
(Please, please) keep your eyes only on me!
わーい！
Yay!
That was our brand new original song, "Ichizutte Trend"!
そう！フワモコのオリジナル曲、一途ってトレンドでしたー！
Yes! That was FUWAMOCO's original song, "Ichizutte Trend"!
どうだったかな？
How was it?
新曲だよー！
It's a brand new song!
And it was written and composed by the amazing Ryujin Kiyoshi-san!
He's written so many songs for idols and voice actors that we really, really love!
So we're so, so honored!
そう！作詞・作曲は清竜人さんでしたー！
Yes! It was written and composed by Ryujin Kiyoshi-san!
清竜人さんにオリジナル曲を書いていただけて光栄です！
We're so honored to have our original song written by Ryujin Kiyoshi-san!
Thank you!
And it's our loviest-doveyist song yet!
So you know, we hope you like it lots and lots!
And it will be released on digital streaming platforms at midnight JST!
Right after this!
We'd be really, really happy if you could listen to it lots and lots!
この配信の後、0時からデジタルリリースされますので、いっぱい聴いてくれると嬉しいな！
It will be digitally released at midnight after this stream, so we'd be happy if you listen to it a lot!
一途ってトレンド！
Ichizutte Trend!
Those are pretty big announcements!
Yeah! Those are pretty big, though!
Yeah, it's our original song!
Yeah!
重大告知だったっけ？
Was it a major announcement?
Oh, what do you think, Ruffians?
No, no, no, no!
We're so excited to have new news!
But wait, we still have something, right?
Did you want to take a look at it?
Uh-huh! Yeah!
Do you want to know what the big announcement is?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah!
じゃあ、モコちゃん、行っちゃおうか！行っちゃおうか！
Then, Moco-chan, shall we do it? Let's do it!
Okay! Okay!
Here we go! せーの... どーん！
Here we go! Ready... Ta-da!
FUWAMOCO 1st Album
FUWAMOCO à la mode 〜いつだってあなたの笑顔を守るのッ〜
[FUWAMOCO à la mode ~forever protecting your smile~]
ON PRE-ORDER NOW!
一生涯、一緒にいたい
I want to be together for a lifetime,
All lifetime, showtime, anytime, bow wow
一生涯 Sing with you...
For a lifetime, singing with you...
めくるめく 迷宮で待ってる
Waiting in the dizzying labyrinth...
背中に君を感じていたいよ
I want to feel you behind me.
ふあふあ もこもこ 魔界乃番犬シスターズ☆★
Fuwa fuwa, moco moco, Demon Guard Dog Sisters!
この世界に爆誕"BAU"DOLです
We are "BAU"DOLS, freshly born into this world!
BAUBAU!!
Bau bau!
私たち、FUWAMOCOのファーストアルバムの発売が決定しました！
Our, FUWAMOCO's, very first album release has been confirmed!
アルバムタイトルは「FUWAMOCO à la mode 〜いつだってあなたの笑顔を守るのッ〜」！
The album title is "FUWAMOCO à la mode ~forever protecting your smile~"!
ジャケットイラストは、イラストレーターの渡辺明夫先生！
The jacket illustration is by illustrator Watanabe Akio-sensei!
FUWAMOCOの憧れの方に描いていただけることになって、本当に嬉しいです！
We're so happy to have our illustration drawn by someone FUWAMOCO looks up to!
オバフ！
Oh, bau!
現在制作中のイラストを特別に見せちゃいます！
We'll show you a special sneak peek of the illustration still in progress!
じゃじゃーん！
Ta-da!
今回のアルバムは、2枚組で作りました！
This album is a 2-disc set!
ディスク1の収録曲は、なんと11曲！新曲もたくさんです！
Disc 1 contains a whopping 11 tracks! Plenty of new songs too!
ディスク2は、アドベントのオリジナル曲のFUWAMOCO歌唱バージョンと、アルバムについて語っているアフターパーティーです！
Disc 2 is FUWAMOCO's vocal version of Advent's original songs, plus an after-party talking about the album!
詳細はまだ内緒だから、続報を待っててね！
The details are still a secret, so stay tuned for more news!
さらにさらに！アルバムには、CD以外のものもたくさん詰め込みました！
And that's not all! We've packed lots of non-CD items into the album too!
キラキラステッカーシート、アクスタ、ポスカ、アナザージャケット...
A sparkly sticker sheet, acrylic stand, postcard, alternate jacket...
そして、二人で心を込めて、ラフィアンズに向けて書いたお手紙！
and a letter written from our hearts to the Ruffians!
そしてそして！二人で頑張って、買ってくれた皆さん全員に、直筆サインを書きます！
And on top of that, we'll work hard to hand-sign every single copy for everyone who buys one!
おおー！
Ohhh!
私たちのファーストアルバム、たくさんの人が聴いてくれたら嬉しいな！
We'd be so happy if lots of people got to listen to our first album!
We have huge news!
Our very first album is finally happening!
The title is FUWAMOCO à la mode ~forever protecting your smile~!
The cover illustration is by Akio Watanabe-sensei, an illustrator we've always looked up to!
We're so happy he agreed to draw for us!
Bau bau!
And we want to show you something special right now! The illustration still in progress!
Ta-da!
This album is a two-disc set!
Disc 1 has 11 songs, and so many brand new ones!
Disc 2 is FUWAMOCO's own vocal version of Advent's original songs, plus an after-party talking all about the album!
But you know, we can't spill any more details yet, so stay tuned!
Mhm!
And that's not all! The album is packed with more than just the CD!
A sparkly sticker sheet, acrylic stand, postcard, alternate jacket, and a letter that the two of us wrote from our hearts just for you!
And you know, the two of us are working hard to hand-sign every single copy for everyone who buys one!
We'd be so happy if lots of Ruffians get to listen to our first album!
Bau bau!
BAUBAU!
We're so happy!
It's finally here! Our album!
ずっと夢見ていたFUWAMOCOのアルバムですよ！
The FUWAMOCO album we've always dreamed of!
ほら！CD！CD！CD！
Look! CD! CD! CD!
Wow, album!
Yeah! This is the album we've always dreamed of, Ruffians!
Ah, this means Moco-chan...
You can hold it in your paws!
We did it!
Hold it...
Yeah!
Thank you, Ruffians!
Thank you for always supporting us!
We're so happy!
いっぱい応援してくれてありがとう！
Thank you so much for always supporting us!
ありがとう！本当にみんなのおかげだよ！
Thank you! It's really all thanks to everyone!
It's thanks to you, Ruffians, that we can do all of these amazing things!
本当にありがとう！
Thank you all so much!
うん、うん！
Yes, yes!
To repeat the important points again...
Pre-orders start very soon!
9 PM JST or 5 AM PDT!
Right after this, okay? Right away! "Right away!"
販売は今日21時、そう、このあとすぐ
Sales start today at 9:00 PM, yes, right after this,
から受注開始します！
pre-orders will begin!
Yeah!
Are you ready? Ready! Yeah!
And, as we mentioned...
Every single CD will be signed by us!
Us! With these paws! Yeah, with these paws!
They're gonna be signed with all of our...
all of our heart!
CD全部、全部、この二人から直筆サインがありますよ！
Every single CD will be hand-signed by the two of us!
書きますよ！
We're going to write them! "Yes!"
心を込めて、大事に作っているアルバムなので、みんなの手元に届いてほしいです！
We put our hearts into making this album, so we hope it reaches everyone's hands!
Please! Take them please! Yeah!
But... this album really means so much to us... so it would mean everything in the world...
...if you could get a copy and add it to your collection...
...and listen to all of our precious songs that we put all of our heart into.
You know... this is the day. The day that we've been dreaming of this entire year of our career!
Thank you! "Thank you so much!"
But, you know, it's not done here yet. No.
We'll continue to work really hard so it will be everything that you dreamed of too, Ruffians, okay?
Thank you, Ruffians!
Are you excited? Yeah! Ruffians, get it right after this, okay?
Don't forget! 忘れないでね！
Don't forget! Don't forget, okay?!
Well, Ruffians... with that, we'd like to continue to sing two final songs for you today.
And, one of those songs... is a senpai's song who we really admire as an idol.
次の曲は、アイドルとして、とっても尊敬していた先輩の曲です。
The next song is by a senpai we deeply respect as an idol.
Ruffians, we hope our feelings reach you.
Please listen to... Aqua Iro Palette!
何しても不器用で
I'm so clumsy in everything that I do,
何かとミスしてばっか
Things go wrong because I make mistakes a lot,
ダメダメな私だって
I feel like I'm so useless,
できることがあるの
But there is still something I can do for you!
凹んで悲しくたって
Even when you are feeling down and sad,
笑顔にしてあげるんだ
I will always make you smile!
ここにいるから早く
I am right here, so please,
私を見つけてね
Hurry and find me!
love you love you. oh oh oh oh oh
i love you. oh oh oh oh oh
ah ~ i love you so much.
Ah~ I love you so much!
love you love you. oh oh oh oh oh
i love you. oh oh oh oh oh
ah ~ 愛してもっと
Ah~ Love me even more!
いつでも隣にいるし
I'll always be right by your side,
いつでも一緒に笑える
We can always laugh together,
私をたくさん知って<
Get to know me even better,
たくさん好きって言って
And tell me you love me lots!
わがままで朝も苦手
I'm selfish and not a morning person,
ドジだしダメダメだけど
I'm clumsy and hopeless, but...
それでも私のことを
Will you still keep your eyes on me?
見つめててね
Keep watching me, okay?
描く 夢の
The path to the future...
未来へ続く
that I've been dreaming of...
道は君と歩けますように
I hope I can walk it together with you!
ねぇもっと！好きになってもらいたいの！
Hey, I want you to love me even more!
頭の中は君ばっか！！
My head is completely filled with you!
ていうかそっぽなんて向いてないで！
I mean, don't look away from me!
あぁもう！ヤキモキしちゃうわ Ah
Ah, geez! You're making me so anxious! Ah~
ずっとずっと好きがいいの
I want you to love me forever and ever!
心の奥もときめいちゃうくらいに
So much that my heart skips a beat deep inside!
こっち向いててよ ねぇダーリン？
Look over here, okay, darling?
あぁもう離さないから、絶対に
Ah, geez, I'll never let you go, absolutely!
love you love you. oh oh oh oh oh
i love you. oh oh oh oh oh
ah ~ 愛してもっと
Ah~ Love me even more!
君がいるから私
Because you are here,
いつでも頑張れるんだ
I can always do my best!
落ち込んで悲しくたって
Even when I'm down and sad,
君がいるから...
because you are here...
君がいるから
Because you are here...
歩いてこられた
...I was able to keep walking.
君がいなくちゃ
If you weren't here,
前も見れない
I wouldn't even be able to look forward.
嫌なこととか 辛いこととか あったって
Even when bad things and painful things happened,
君の力で ここまで笑ってこれたんだ
with your strength, I was able to laugh through it all.
今度はもっと 私がずっと引っ張って
This time, I'll be the one to keep pulling you forward,
連れて行くんだ
and take you along with me!
君がいるから
Because you are here,
私がいるの
I am here too.
こんな私を愛して くれる？
Will you love someone like me?
ねぇ もっと ねえ もっと まだ もっと 受け止めてよね ねえいい？
Hey, accept me more, and more, and even more, okay?
さあ 声を上げて
Come on, raise your voice!
ねぇもっと
Hey, more...
ねぇもっと 好きになってもらいたいの
Hey, I want you to love me even more!
いつでもそう 私ばっかりみたいに
Just like how I'm always looking only at you,
そっぽなんて向かせないわ
I won't let you look away!
ねえほら 夢中にしちゃうわ ああ
See, I'll make you fall head over heels for me!
ずっとずっと好きでいいの？
Is it okay to love you forever and ever?
心も体も染まっちゃうくらいに
So much that my heart and body are stained in your color.
こっち向いててよね ダーリン
Keep looking at me, darling,
あともう 離さないから
because I'll never let you go again.
絶対に
Absolutely,
絶対ね
definitely,
絶対よ
for sure!
約束だよ
It's a promise!
We LOVE you so much, 大〜すきRuffians!!
[On-Screen] We LOVE you so much, we love you so much, Ruffians!!
We'll continue to do our ALL to protect your smiles as "BAUDOLS" ずっと笑顔をまもるよ!!
[On-Screen] We'll continue to do our ALL to protect your smiles as 'BAUDOLS'!
愛しちゃうもっと
I'll love you even more!
This song is our last song!
Let's send our love to Aqua-senpai, Ruffians!
いつの間にか見つけてた遠い夢
Before I knew it, I had found a distant dream,
一人じゃ見えなかった景色
a view that I couldn't have seen alone.
波打つ風の音と加速していく想いに
With the sound of the swaying wind and my accelerating feelings,
戸惑いを覚えた
I felt bewildered.
ずっと追いかけた理想の姿は
The ideal self that I've always chased after
まだ届かなくて遠いけど
is still far out of reach, but...
きっとこの瞬間はかけがえのないみんなで
Surely, this moment is irreplaceable. With everyone,
共に行くよ
we will go together!
手を繋いで 3・2・1！
Let's hold hands, 3, 2, 1!
輝き宿して
Harboring a shine,
夢の場所へ
to the place of our dreams!
駆け抜けていく僕たちの青春の光は
The light of our youth running through
誰にも止められないよ
cannot be stopped by anyone!
笑い合う分だけ (優しく)
As much as we laugh together (gently),
零れる涙さえ (今)
even the spilling tears (now),
ほら輝かせ明日へ運ぶから
look, we'll make them shine and carry them to tomorrow.
君の隣へ
Right next to you,
僕たちは世界を超えていく
we will go beyond the world.
迎えに行くよ
We're coming to meet you.
まだ見えない明日も
Even the tomorrow we can't see yet,
キラめきに変えてきっと
we'll surely turn it into glitter.
僕たちが未来へと
To the future, we
連れて行くから
will take you with us!
背伸びしては手を伸ばす憧れの
Stretching my back and reaching out towards my longing,
行き先示す星になろう
I'll become the star that points the way.
つまずくその度に 手を差し伸べ合えたら
If we can reach out our hands to each other every time we stumble,
すぐに届くはずさ
we should reach it in no time.
そっと踏み出した
The small step we quietly took,
小さな勇気は
the tiny bit of courage,
もう消えないように繋ごう
let's connect them so they never fade away.
不安も愛しさも大切に抱きしめて
Cherishing and embracing both our anxiety and love,
共に行くよ
we will go together!
目を合わせて 3・2・1！
Let's lock eyes, 3, 2, 1!
晴れ渡る希望へ
Toward the clear-skied hope,
飛び出せるよ
we can leap forward!
突き抜けていく僕たちの透き通る決意は
Our transparent determination breaking through
まだまだ止められないよ
cannot be stopped just yet!
歩き足りない今日こそ (トキメキ)
On this day when we haven't walked enough (excitement),
に変えてもっと
let's turn it into a heartbeat and go further!
僕たちがいつまでも
We will always and forever
背中を押すから
push your back!
Ruffians! We have something we want to share with you!
It's now been three years since we made our debut here in hololive!
There's been so many precious memories made!
Laughed together, and even some tears that we've lost track of too.
There's been lots of challenges, but it's all been worth it!
The many, many dreams we talked about three years ago have been coming true, one by one.
And now, our dream of our very own first album is coming true too!
Yeah! We're so excited, we might explode!
We want to continue on this journey, no matter what comes our way!
As long as we're together, we know that we can do the impossible!
Yeah!
Thank you for being our precious Ruffians, here by our side.
We'll continue to protect your smiles forever and ever!
Yeah! Bau bau!
ずっと一人で描いていた
I was always drawing it all by myself,
いつからかこんなに
But somewhere along the way...
一人じゃないって思えて
...I realized I wasn't alone.
少しずつ
Little by little,
芽生える大好きを紡ぎ
spinning the love that begins to sprout,
どこまでも
no matter how far,
高く
and how high,
あおいろの空へ
toward the blue sky...
駆け抜けていく
We will run through,
僕たちの
Our...
青春の光は
...youthful light...
誰にも止められないよ
...cannot be stopped by anyone!
笑い合う日も
Even on days we laugh together,
こぼれる涙さえ
and even through falling tears,
ほら輝かせて
look, we will make them shine,
明日へ運ぶから
carrying them toward tomorrow,
君の隣へ
right to your side.
僕たちは
We are going to...
世界を超えていく
...cross over the world,
迎えに行くよ
coming to meet you!
まだ見えない明日も
Even the tomorrow we cannot see yet,
きらめきに変えて保存
we'll turn it into a sparkle,
きっと
surely...
僕たちが
...we will...
未来へと
...head toward the future,
果てのない
...toward the endless...
未来へと
...future,
連れていくから
because we will take you there!
We're together FURR-EVER!! It's all Thanks to hololive
Thank you for 3 Years!!